[{"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "mango", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "orange", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "orange", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{2;3;5};{6;8;9};{1;4;7}}|{{2;4;6};{3;7;8};{1;5;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "banana", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{1;2;3};{6;7;8};{4;5;9}}|{{5;6;8};{3;4;7};{1;2;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "banana", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "peach", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{2;3;7};{1;8;9};{4;5;6}}|{{1;2;4};{3;7;8};{5;6;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "peach", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{4;5;7};{1;2;3};{6;8;9}}|{{5;6;8};{3;4;9};{1;2;7}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "pear", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "pear", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "pear", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{2;5;8};{3;7;9};{1;4;6}}|{{1;4;9};{3;7;8};{2;5;6}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "lemon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "banana", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "banana", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "banana", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{3;8;9};{1;4;5};{2;6;7}}|{{1;3;8};{2;5;9};{4;6;7}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "orange", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "peach", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "orange", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "peach", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{1;7;9};{2;4;6};{3;5;8}}|{{2;5;7};{3;4;9};{1;6;8}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "peach", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "orange", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "orange", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "orange", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{3;4;5};{2;7;9};{1;6;8}}|{{1;2;6};{4;5;7};{3;8;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "banana", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "banana", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "mango", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{6;7;9};{1;5;8};{2;3;4}}|{{3;5;7};{2;8;9};{1;4;6}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "apple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "peach", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "peach", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "apple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "peach", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "apple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{6;8;9};{1;3;4};{2;5;7}}|{{1;5;9};{2;7;8};{3;4;6}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "pear", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "pear", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "mango", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pear", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "watermelon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/西瓜_1.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{3;4;6};{2;7;8};{1;5;9}}|{{4;5;7};{1;3;8};{2;6;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "pear", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "lemon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "orange", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "pear", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pear", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{1;4;8};{2;3;7};{5;6;9}}|{{2;5;8};{3;6;9};{1;4;7}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "lemon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "lemon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "lemon", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "mango", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{6;7;9};{2;3;5};{1;4;8}}|{{2;3;6};{4;5;9};{1;7;8}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "orange", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "apple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "apple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "orange", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桔子_1.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "apple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "mango", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{4;7;9};{1;2;8};{3;5;6}}|{{1;8;9};{2;3;6};{4;5;7}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "apple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "apple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "banana", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "apple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/黄苹果.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "banana", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "banana", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/开口香蕉_1.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{2;5;9};{1;4;8};{3;6;7}}|{{3;6;7};{1;2;5};{4;8;9}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "mango", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "peach", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "peach", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "peach", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/桃子.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "mango", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/芒果.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{3;5;7};{1;4;8};{2;6;9}}|{{5;6;7};{2;4;9};{1;3;8}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "lemon", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "blueberry", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/蓝莓.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "lemon", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/柠檬.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{4;6;8};{2;3;7};{1;5;9}}|{{1;3;9};{5;7;8};{2;4;6}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}, {"body": [{"title": "拖拽分类", "stem": "按形状/水果种类分类。", "classifyType": "cardShape", "typeList": [{"order": 1, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 2, "type": "pear", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 3, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 4, "type": "pear", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 5, "type": "strawberry", "shape": "triangle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/草莓_1.svg"}, {"order": 6, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 7, "type": "pear", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/梨.svg"}, {"order": 8, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "square", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}, {"order": 9, "type": "pineapple", "shape": "circle", "src": "v2/通用/水果/菠萝.svg"}], "type": "au-classify-byshape"}], "answers": "({{2;7;9};{1;6;8};{3;4;5}}|{{2;4;7};{6;8;9};{1;3;5}})", "knowledges": ["按不同的标准分类"], "resource": "resource", "type": "操作", "explain": "explain", "level": "3", "number": "1-4-2-4"}]